キルアが　宮殿に突入した瞬間 思ったことは… やっぱりな
Gon, Kurapika, and Leorio have advanced a little closer to the mansion.
…であった
Meanwhile...
目の前には　１階にいるはずのない ユピーが立っているという あり得ない場面
I'm home.
打ち合わせの段階で 検討にすら挙がらなかった状況に 直面しても
Well, no one's around.
経験によって キルアは平静を保てた
Welcome back. How did work go?
何だ？　こいつらは どこから湧いた？
Does that mean you dispatched your target?
あり得ない場面は　ユピーに とっても同様であったが
I'm sure you were watching me
from a distance.
ユピーは すぐに考えるのをやめた
Mom's waiting for you inside. I don't want to see her.
それに由来するのか 他の２匹に比べ　個に頓着がなく
Did you need something?
だが　無我故の強さを持つ
I wanted to say hello. Are you new here?
ユピーが　形態変化と 好戦的な笑みを見せた時
While you were away,
I was hired as an apprentice butler. My name is Canary. Here. You can have this.
シュートは　動きを止めた
No, thank you. But I appreciate the thought, Killua-sama.
しかし　それは シュートが精神的に
I cannot do that. I am a servant.
遅れをとったからではない
And you are my employer.
これ以上　接近すると 奴は　俺を迎え撃つ
Tsk... That's lame.
前にいるはずのナックル達に 命中したら…
You were using the Shadow Step, right?
ユピーの注意を さらに自分へ向けるため
The technique where you move silently,
so you won't be noticed.
飛ぶ腕とカゴを 操作しようとした瞬間
It's one of the first assassination
techniques we learn
それは来た ハッ！
in the Zoldyck family. Is that so?
これは　「ドラゴンダイヴ」！
It's a city that has been erased from this world.
じいさんの知人って…
Huh, never heard of it.
唯一　解答を得たキルアが それ故　一瞬固まる
You're allowed to dump anything in Meteor City. That's why many members
事情を知らぬ者の衝撃は それ以上である
of the mafia and the Phantom
Troupe come from there. I'd like to visit some time.
その中で　ただ２名
When you visit, I can serve as your guide.
バカな！ 暴走!?
I'll teach you the Rhythm Echo.
お前の相手は ユピーじゃねえだろ！
Rhythm Echo?
いや　違う
It's a technique that utilizes the Shadow Step.
やや遅れて　キルアが さらに　コンマ数秒遅れて 他の者が理解する
You move at a certain rhythm,
creating afterimages. I see...
あの野郎　この状況で
It appears we have intruders.
何て早く　何てとこに 気付きやがるんだ！
Many intruders. Let Mike handle it.
万が一 メレオロンとナックルが
The master has ordered that
Mike be restrained today.
「神の共犯者」を発動したまま この龍の矢に貫かれ
They wish to test my abilities.
それとも　死後 さらに強まる「念」として
We'll split up and look for their mansion.
答えは　分からない
Leave.
仮に　後者が正解ならば
Who are you?
今　２人が無事かどうかを 確かめるすべはない
There is no need for me to answer that question. You are trespassing on private property.
万が一の場合　代わりに誰かが
I cannot allow you to pass without permission.
ユピーと　やらなければならない
Can you stop us?
本来ならば俺の役目
It's obvious that you stand no chance.
ゴン！ シュートに落ち度はない
Well, if you don't resist, we'll spare your life.
俺すら　気付いて動くのは キルアより遅かった
If you take one step past this line, I shall use force to remove you.
シュート　自分を責めるな
What was that? You can stand back and watch, boss...
精神を立て直すんだ！
We'll take care of this.
ゴンとキルアがユピーなら
Let's go!
お前がピトーだぞ！
Don't mock us!
あれが　ゴンだ！
Bitch! Get her!
そんな自分が嫌だった
Do you wish to continue?
でも　直せなかった
After all that, she hasn't
even broken a sweat...
仲間　師の言葉ですら
Are you a member of the Zoldyck family?
強い者の理屈と 本当には聞いていなかった
Hardly. I am but an apprentice butler.
けど…　なのに！ 俺より　ひと回り以上 弱かった　お前が
With your abilities, you're not even a match for the butlers, let alone the Zoldyck family.
俺の檻を壊してくれた
A futile effort...
弱い傾向があった 生きて　お前に言う 「ありがとう」と！
I'm telling you that it's useless!
ナックル達は…
Die!
何だ？
Could you clean this up? Sure, that's my job.
どいつだ？ 誰に攻撃された？
Plus, Mike is starving.
飛び道具？　死角からか？
H-Help!
「ハコワレ」　発動！
You already knew the Rhythm Echo.
「神の共犯者」と「ハコワレ」の コンボが可能であることは
Yes... Forgive me.
無論　事前に検証を終えている
You think you're stronger than I am.
「神の共犯者」の発動中に
Absolutely not.
ユピーが　ポットクリンを 認識するすべはない 故に　ユピーが疑問を棚上げし
Really? So, I don't have anyone to play with.
押し寄せる敵に 集中せんとしたのは 至極　当然の流れである
Will you be my friend, Canary?
ここまでは 討伐軍の思惑通りであった
Tsk. Lame...
しかし　見事　初撃を 打ち込んだはずのナックルに 戦慄　走る！
Let's be friends!
戦歴５０００を超える 経験と勘から
Hunter Vocabulary
相手の力量を数値化して来た ナックルにとって
Canary
決して珍しくはない
Is she okay? Yeah.
天秤の対として 軽過ぎるほどの力を持つ敵
Wake up!
はるか膨大なオーラを 内包する怪物
Oh. Morning, Bro.
くっ… ボスの５倍!?　１０倍!?
What time is it? Don't be too arrogant, Kil!
それ以上!?
What?
分からねえ！
I feel really bad about stabbing you, Bro.
前代未聞の経験である
Sorry. It was the wrong thing to do, Bro.
仮に　１０倍の
You can tell?
７０万オーラだとすると
Tsk! Hello?
奴をとばすまでに一体…
Oh, Mama? Uh-huh.
王！
Kil, your friends are near the butler's office.
その時…
If I ask Mama, those three can become...
ピトーの まがまがしいオーラが
Milluki.
討伐軍の全身を覆った その　こわばりを ユピーは見逃さなかった
If you so much as touch them, I'll kill you.
王！
Forgive me for not introducing myself.
王！ あっ…。
Why can't Killua come see us? Because he's in solitary confinement. Solitary confinement?
翼を持たぬピトーにとって 空中という 落下の他に選択肢のない状態が
And he voluntarily entered
solitary confinement. So we do not know when he will leave...
逆に幸いしたといえるだろう
What? Father! What are you doing?!
行動に制限がなければ ピトーもまた　プフと同様
Don't do anything hasty! He's finally returned!
全力で　王の元へ向かうのが 護衛軍の心情として自然であり
I'm coming in.
その際 「円」を使う余裕があるかは
One Kill Per Day
甚だ疑問である
That's enough, Mil.
結果…
But, Grandpa Zeno...
西塔２階　迎賓の間
Okay.
あっ！
But I do feel bad.
奴らも 「円」を使って王の位置を…
Kil, Silva wants to see you. Dad?
この時　ピトーは 自軍が置かれている現状の
Okay.
この上ない深刻さに気付いた
Damn it!
瞬間　ピトーは 四足獣本来のごとく　身を丸め
You always spoil Kil, Grandpa!
鋼のような大腿部が
That's why he's such an uppity brat...
かつて　カイトを襲撃する直前に 見せたこわばりの
He's special.
倍ほどに膨れ上がった
Mil, what do you think of Kil's potential?
曲者よりも速く 王の元へ参じるために
Considerable praise. But he fails as an assassin because he's so moody.
しかし　その直後… あっ…！
A kid who wants to make friends
can't lead the Zoldyck family.
跳躍を一瞬　後悔するほどの 暗霊とした負のエネルギーが
That is true... Right? Take me.
向かう場を中心として
I'll kill anyone I'm asked to.
発散されていることに 気付かされる
Oh, that's right.
これが　王の…
The bomb I'll use next time
is awesome, Grandpa! It's super-compact.
主君の発しているオーラは
I attached it to a female mosquito, and it's triggered to explode when the
mosquito sucks the target's blood.
今の精神状態が　容易に くみ取れるくらいに警戒がなく
But the problem is getting the mosquito
to recognize the target...
それ故に　現況が途方もなく 想像以上に悪い方向へ 進行していることを
Mil... You're a bright boy, but that foolish nature of yours doesn't help.
痛感せざるを得なかった
Oh, why must Father be this way?
大階段が　崩れ落ちた
How about we tail them? Sure, but if we do that, she'll take the blame.
王が視線を切ると
It was easy.
再び　時が動き始めた
Kil, come over here.
いや　王以外の時間は 凍ったままである
Huh? I want you to tell me more.
王をとらんと侵入して来た はずの　曲者までが 固唾をのんで　足を止めた理由は
Who did you meet? How did you feel? You can tell me anything...
血に染まる少女
Okay.
そして　その体を抱く
I can't believe this.
異形なる者の所作　全てが 見紛うことなく 優しさにあふれていたからに 他ならない
Father didn't even ask me first. Oh, Kil seems to be having fun with Papa... I won't forgive them!
ピトー。
pointed a blade at Gon's forehead,
but Gon still...
はっ。
Kil.
通常の王の表情に戻っていた
Huh? Do you want to see your friends?
それが逆に ピトーを不安にさせた
You don't need to hold back.
コムギを治せ。 頼んだぞ。
Tell me the truth. Thinking back, we've never had a father-son chat before.
敵の動きを　ただ　立ち止まって 見守るという愚挙を
You are my son. But you are your own person. Live as you please.
百戦錬磨の２人が続けたのは 敬意の表れである
If you get tired, you can come home.
一個の生命に対する 慈愛あふれる振る舞い
Uh-huh. I understand.
これを侵しては そもそもの大儀を失い 人ですら　なくなる
But... Promise me one thing. Never betray your friends.
ゼノが　そう問い詰めるのも 無理はない
Never.
同様の思いは ネテロにもあった
Kil.
ここでは…。
It's too late. Those three left. Return to your cell.
場所を変えるか。
No way. I'm leaving. Kil!
うぬらも同じであろう？
Out of my way.
そのために巨額を費やし ゼノの力を借りたネテロである 異存のあるはずもない
Oh, Kil... Your eyes are so cold now...
先手をとられたという思いは 拭えない
What were you thinking? Kil was finally home!
「ドクターブライス」。
No! What are you saying? This is a critical juncture in the process of determining if he's qualified
to lead the family!
ピトーが 能力を発動した瞬間…
So you understand what's at stake. Then stop griping, and keep your mouth shut!
致命的な油断
He'll come home one day.
一瞬　２人が そう覚悟したのも無理はない
Because he is my son.
それほどに　たやすく　悠然と
But Silva declares that Killua
will return as an assassin.
王は　２人の死線を横切った
Meanwhile, Gon and his friends
head to the butler's office.
敵もまた　はるか怪物
Will they be able to see Killua?